{
    "subject": "resource/Santa_Maria_Coghinas",
    "predicate": "ontology/region",
    "object": "resource/Sardinia",
    "human_readable": "Santa Maria Coghinas is located in Sardinia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9158290028572083,
            "question": "Where is Santa Maria Coghinas located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7156755328178406,
            "question": "What region is Santa Maria Coghinas part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5461977124214172,
            "question": "What island is Santa Maria Coghinas on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.540913462638855,
            "question": "Is Santa Maria Coghinas in Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5246806740760803,
            "question": "Are there any famous landmarks near Santa Maria Coghinas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31009772419929504,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Santa Maria Coghinas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3092782497406006,
            "question": "Can you name a city or town on the island of Sardinia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28050681948661804,
            "question": "What are some popular activities for tourists visiting Santa Maria Coghinas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18218475580215454,
            "question": "Does Santa Maria Coghinas have a rich history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16629767417907715,
            "question": "What is the main language spoken in Santa Maria Coghinas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Santa Maria Coghinas is located in Sardinia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5575_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Santa Maria Coghinas have a rich history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5575_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular activities for tourists visiting Santa Maria Coghinas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5575_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a city or town on the island of Sardinia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5575_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5575_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the location of Santa Maria Coghinas, mentioning that it is situated in the Sardinia region, which supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Santa Maria Coghinas is located in Italy, Sardinia, Sassari, which confirms that it is indeed located in Sardinia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}